A Guide to the L.F. Payne, Jr. Papers, 1988-1997
Library of Virginia
- Series VII. Special Media, 1988-1997., Extent: 2 boxes. (Box 83-84)
  - Videotape - John Hager Campaign Ad, Hager Affirmative Action Issue, WWBT Richmond Channel 12, October 1997, Monday Night Football, Stock Market Drop, ABC "Nightline" and ABC News Special, 27 October 1997. (Box 84)
  - Videotape - L.F. Payne for Lt. Governor (Greer, Margolis) "Fight" and "Blue Ridge". (Box 84)
  - Videotape - L.F. Payne for Lt. Governor (Greer, Margolis) "Choose" (Two Copies). (Box 84)
  - Videotape - L.F. Payne for Lt. Governor (Greer, Margolis) "Tax" (Two Copies). (Box 84)
  - Videotape - L.F. Payne for Lt. Governor (GMMB & A Inc.) Avid Rough Cuts, Blue Ridge Versions A, B, Boy Scout. (Box 84)
  - Videotape - L.F. Payne for Lt. Governor (GMMB & A Inc.) Avid Rough Cuts, Blue Ridge Version 1, 1 Alt, and 2. (Box 84)
  - Videotape - L.F. Payne for Lt. Governor (GMMB & A Inc.) Avid Rough Cuts, Blue Bridge/Portrait, Blue Ridge/Education, Blue Ridge/Main St.. (Box 84)
  - Videotape - L.F. Payne for Lt. Governor (GMMB & A Inc.) Blue Ridge Alt. Rough Cut. (Box 84)
  - Videotape - L.F. Payne for Lt. Governor (GMMB & A Inc.) Blue Ridge 2. (Box 84)
  - Videotape - L.F. Payne for Lt. Governor (GMMB & A Inc.) "Endorse". (Box 84)
  - Videotape - L.F. Payne for Lt. Governor (GMMB & A Inc.) Avid Rough Cuts, "Trooper," "Values/Education," "Fight". (Box 84)
  - Videotape - L.F. Payne for Lt. Governor (GMMB & A Inc.) Avid Rough Cuts, "Trooper," "Values/Education," "Fight A and B". (Box 84)
  - Videotape - L.F. Payne for Lt. Governor (GMMB & A Inc.) "Levels". (Box 84)
  - Videotape - L.F. Payne with Richard Real, Richmond Channel 8, 29 June 1997. (Box 84)
  - Videotape - "A Visit With LF Payne" Prestige Channel 3 News, Fredericksburg, 15 August 1997. (Box 84)
  - Videotape - L.F. Payne on NAFTA Vote, Dateline WVIR Charlottesville Channel 29 News. (Box 84)
  - Videotape - Virginia State Police Graduation Exercises. (Box 84)
  - Videotape - "My Visit with Santa" Holiday Cartoon Classics Vol.1. (Box 84)
  - Videotape - "Chance Favors the Prepared Mind" - Reflections on Coach John McKenna. (Box 84)